{
    "id": "f2ed0fac0be94177a0d307414a5963f4",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You needn’t have brought …………………. that topic again.",
            "description": "To bring up a topic is to mention it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you didn’t get the right answer, you should do the sum …………………….",
            "description": "To do over is to do again. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "back"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Here is my glass. Please fill it ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to be friends with anyone who says nasty things about me behind my …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "head",
                "eyes"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief guest gave ……………………….. the prices.",
            "description": "To give away is to distribute.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better give me my money …………………………",
            "description": "To give money back is to repay.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "back",
                "again"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is very cold. Put your coat …………………..",
            "description": "To put on a coat is to wear it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The firemen worked hard to put the fire ………………………….",
            "description": "To put out fire is to extinguish it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Please take ………………………. my number.",
            "description": "To take down is to write down.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Once you have finished playing, put the toys …………………….",
            "description": "To put something away is to put it in the proper place after use.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "out",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know why they turned ……………………… my application.",
            "description": "To turn down is to reject. ",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "in",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His grandmother passed …………………… in July.",
            "description": "To pass away is to die.",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}